FILING FOR LOVE
How could you miss something
this mundane?
Not even a rookie would do this.
Get a hold of yourself!
Order within an organization
is built on rank.
However...
the true power game between these two
goes much deeper
and far more quietly.
TECHNICAL HIGH SCHOOL
Does a completely equal relationship
even exist?
When two or more come together,
a hierarchy forms.
Even between friends and lovers
an imbalance of power is
almost inevitable.
And everyone
desires to rise higher,
even if only a little.
Good job, everyone.
Sometimes
at the risk of doing things
they shouldn't.
Gosh, that tastes so sweet.
What's that?
- What's what?
- What is it?
- Something's hovering outside.
- Where?
You see something?
You're quite photogenic
Director Kang.
Are you the police?
No, I'm not.
I'm...
NOH KI-JUN
I'm with the Audit Team
at the head office.
Stop what you were doing
and follow me for a chat
Director Kang.
INTERVIEW ROOM
AUDIT IN PROGRESS
I heard Haemu's Audit Team
can bring down birds in flight.
I see you send your own birds now.
And you're about to crash and burn.
- Hey, you!
- It's Assistant Manager Noh
from Audit Team One.
How dare an assistant manager
harass a director?
Do you think you're the police?
The National Intelligence Service?
This is illegal filming.
I'll sue you and your whole team
for invasion of privacy.
It's the least I can do to catch
a spy who's selling core tech
to an overseas competitor.
We have our own struggles, too.
It's always the unethical ones
who are obsessed
with privacy and personal rights.
Hey, listen.
Don't go too far.
Even if I were an industrial spy,
this is just my first offense.
So if I act remorseful
I'll most likely be let off
on probation.
Director Kang.
He speaks pretty good Korean,
didn't he?
Because he's an ethnic Korean
from China.
You could say he's Korean.
A North Korean.
Turns out this company was
a source of funding for North Korea.
It was disguised
as a foreign-currency operation
but it was actually run
by North Korea.
Oh, dear.
If you're charged with espionage,
that means
you're not an industrial spy anymore
but an actual spy.
Probation?
You'll most likely go to prison.
Darn it.
- Oh, no.
- Don't do that.
Will you calm down?
This is so infuriating!
You punks. I said it wasn't me.
Why won't you believe me?
- Calm down, sir. We got a tip-off...
- "Calm down"?
- We got a tip-off.
- A tip-off? What tip-off?
I'm being framed, okay?
Something's always going on
at Team Three.
What is it this time?
Someone sent an anonymous note
to Team Three saying
he hid the fact that he was married
and approached her.
As proof, she said
he has a mole down there.
- What?
- Down there.
Right there.
Haemu Group.
The 7th largest business in Korea
and 9th in sales.
The top-ranking department
in this conglomerate
with 42 subsidiaries.
Even the head office's Audit Team
has a hierarchy of its own.
Audit Team One and Two
handle major cases
such as embezzlement
malpractice, collusion,
and information leaks.
Audit Team Three...
I'm not in the mood for coffee!
Okay, fine. Get your hands off me.
- Hands off.
- Okay.
I'll show you.
- No, don't!
No!
Don't!
Shoot.
- Look!
- Oh, come on...
Look carefully.
Do you see a mole?
- Don't cover it.
- What's his issue?
I'm innocent.
This is what they do.
EPISODE 1:
UP&DOWN
Hello, sir. Good morning.
If it isn't Noh Ki-jun,
the gentleman.
You're having
a handsome start to the day.
Thank you.
- Have a great day.
- You, too.
SAFEGUARDING CORE TECHNOLOGY
FROM INDUSTRIAL SPIES
HAEMU'S AUDIT TEAM
Auditing increases
and improves the value
of the company's business execution.
NOH KI-JUN AKA MR. SMILES,
ASSISTANT MANAGER, AUDIT TEAM 1
Oh, wow.
"Mr. Smiles"?
We can't have those
in the Audit Team.
I didn't come up with it, okay?
What's wrong with it?
It gives me pride
that my colleague is
the face of the Audit Team.
To be honest, Team Three yesterday
was a huge embarrassment.
They let a guy
drop his pants in the office.
It was utter madness.
I dreamed of it, even.
That guy's thing.
- Oh, the shudders.
- Get out of my head.
- It's just gimbap.
- Sorry. My bad.
- Sorry.
- Anyway...
Why should we handle stuff like that?
It's not at all dignified.
We must look into everything
we get a tip-off on.
That's why we have Team Three.
Team One and Two
do all the important stuff
and Team Three
gets the trivial stuff.
They go on stakeouts
to see how long people smoke
and poop during work hours.
Once I saw them go around
all the break rooms
to count the coffee mix packets.
That's so depressing.
People think our Audit Team
is powerful enough
to bring down birds from the sky.
- Team Three...
- Not Team Three.
They're more like poop-scoops.
I like the ring of that. Poop-scoops.
What if someone were to hear you?
It's Executive Assistant Park.
- Gosh.
- My word.
Hello, Ms. Park.
Isn't it a lovely day?
It is.
We got to see her before work.
I have a good feeling about today.
I'll go ahead.
You guys finish breakfast.
What? You're going already?
What's my afternoon schedule?
You have a meeting
with Haemu Media's executives.
I like your tie.
You have a good eye, sir.
- Ki-jun.
- Hey.
Ki-jun.
Our team saw the PR clip,
and everyone's raving
and wondering who you are.
Really? They'll swoon
if they see me in person.
What are you doing today after work?
How about a drink?
I heard a nice wine bar
opened nearby.
- Where is it?
- It's called...
I'll be in touch, okay?
Wait, Ki-jun.
14TH FLOOR
PLANNING TEAM, AUDIT TEAM
What the heck?
Ji-hye...
That's way too passionate a greeting
after a long break.
I missed you.
Will you meet up
with that other girl later?
Hang out with me.
No, wait. What?
Aren't you getting married?
You called it off?
Not exactly.
I feel a bit down.
The idea that I'll be stuck
with one guy for the rest of my life.
How about
we have a good time
just one last time?
I'm not that kind of guy.
It's natural to feel uneasy
before the wedding.
I'll entertain you instead.
With a hefty cash envelope.
What the heck is that?
How much will you gift me?
Hey.
- What are you doing?
- Hey, Mr. Noh.
Look at that. It's in bloom.
I wonder who's watering
and looking after it.
It's doing so well
in this desolate place.
Gosh, you're very sentimental.
I'm sure you don't care.
Because your life's in full bloom.
Ms. Hong from HR just told me.
You might get a special promotion
for catching Director Kang.
Is that true?
- I can't say.
- Wait a minute. I guess it's true.
You were Director Kim's favorite
when he was Head of Audit.
I trust you'll look out for me
later on.
Don't forget that, okay?
Guys, have you heard the news?
What news?
People are losing their minds
here and there.
A really scary rumor is going around.
It's code red right now.
What's going on?
Joo In-a
is back.
Isn't that Joo In-a?
- For real?
- It really is her.
HAEMU INTRANET
1 NEW MESSAGE FROM MR. KIM
She must be back.
NEW MESSAGE
NEW NOTIFICATION
What's going on?
YOU GOT A NEW MESSAGE
She actually came back.
- What's happening?
- What do you think?
- Joo In-a's here.
- Joo's here.
- We're done for.
- Is she back for good?
- What a disaster.
- I'll be damned.
I HATE GETTING CC-ED TO EMAILS
WILL OVERSEAS BRANCHES SUFFER?
ALL SITES ARE ON STANDBY
HOW WILL THIS CHANGE THINGS?
I WONDER IF THE EXECUTIVES ARE AFRAID
You know, at work
you must beware
of those with nicknames.
People give nicknames
to badmouth freely.
I bet Joo In-a has
a dozen or so nicknames.
"Joo In-Out" is a famous one.
Get on her bad side and you're out.
I thought that was funny.
"Joo-tergeist."
She's like a poltergeist
that stays at work day and night.
I heard she earned a new nickname
- while working overseas.
- What's that?
She fought a gang
over a business license.
They called her
"Joo-sniper."
She actually fired a gun?
I'm sure it's just a rumor.
How could something like that
even become a rumor?
What's most important is
which division she'll join.
Don't you think?
JOO'S IN THE ELEVATOR
KIM JIN-HEE FROM PLANNING:
She's in the elevator.
Which floor did she press?
JOO'S IN THE ELEVATOR
WHICH FLOOR DID SHE PRESS?
She's smashing the Close Door button.
I think my heart
is getting smashed, too.
Passed the fourth floor.
Fifth floor.
Passed the sixth floor!
Where the heck is she going?
Did HR post a notice?
No, not yet.
HR AND INFORMATION OFFICE
HEAD OF HR, HAEMU GROUP
BOO SE-YOUNG
WOULD YOU LIKE TO PROCEED?
APPROVAL OF APPOINTMENT,
JOO IN-A, DEPARTMENT HEAD
CANCEL
APPROVE
Ninth floor.
Tenth floor.
Why does she keep coming up?
AS LONG AS
SHE DOESN'T GET OFF WITH ME
JOO IN-A, PLEASE GET OFF
WHY'S THE ELEVATOR SO SLOW TODAY?
PHEW, I'M GETTING OFF FIRST
I'M SO JEALOUS
PASSED 13TH FLOOR
WILL SHE GET OFF HERE?
14TH FLOOR...
It's the 14th floor!
Stay calm, everyone!
The Planning Office is
on the 14th floor, too.
PLANNING OFFICE
Put everything away.
Hey, get rid of all the dust.
Wipe every single speck.
Dump all the documents
and scrap papers on your desk.
And your coffees!
Drink it up and dump the cups.
Is there a Kim Gyu-yeong?
ONE-DAY COURIER
What are you doing to me?
It's nice to meet you all.
I'm Joo In-a, the new Head of Audit.
Come on, now.
Why the dull atmosphere?
How about I sing a song
to lighten things up?
Thank you for the warm welcome.
Nice to meet you.
Manager Kwon Myeong-jin.
Yes. I'm pleased to meet you.
You sound overly pleased. Relax.
I will. Sorry.
I'm Mun Gyeong-jin,
assistant team leader of Team One.
You're an assistant team leader?
You look young for that title.
I hope we get on well.
I'm Kim Tae-hwan,
Leader of Audit Team Two.
- I hope we can work well.
- I really hope so.
Let's try to get along.
Jeong Dong-min,
assistant team leader of Team Two.
I hope we get along.
I'm Ju Yeon-u,
senior associate of Team One.
Which Ju clan
does your surname belong to?
Well...
Is it from the word "juice"?
Yes, you're right.
I hope we get along.
Wait, she's pretty normal.
There are too many groundless rumors.
Right. We got scared for no reason.
Hello.
I'm Sung Doo-gi,
a senior associate on Team One.
I hope we work well together!
I love your energy.
- Let's work well together.
- Thank you.
I'm Assistant Manager Ahn Min-su
from the same team.
I hope to impress you.
I look forward
to your impressive work.
Thank you.
Hello, I'm Assistant Manager
Noh Ki-jun of Audit Team One.
Assistant Manager Noh Ki-jun.
Shall we get to work?
Excuse me, Ms. Joo?
I'm sorry to bother you
when you just came in.
No problem. Give that to me.
It's a routine audit notification.
I need to send it right away.
Please approve it for me.
Haemu Industries.
You've audited them
for five years in a row.
Yes, that's right.
I've been in charge since my transfer
here from Haemu Industries.
You've been auditing
your former boss for five years.
Yes.
You can stop now.
It must be boring for both parties.
Our new rule that is no one audits
the same subsidiary
for more than two years.
One year if you used to work there.
I get what you're saying, Ms. Joo.
I know better than anyone
how they do business.
I also know
which areas are usually corrupt.
How corrupt is that place
that you couldn't
get to the bottom of it
for five years?
Pardon?
Well, Ms. Joo.
- What I mean is...
- You laughed?
I told you to stop going.
That's all you have to do.
Why do you talk back at every turn?
Do you think I'm here to have
a lengthy discussion with you?
If you know
about Haemu Industries that well
why did you only do
a brief look-over every year?
You haven't found anything
that led to disciplinary action.
You worked there for over ten years.
You just couldn't bear
to punish anyone.
No, it's not that at all.
Then did you collude with them
to hide a sweet slush fund somewhere?
Shall I go digging myself?
To see if you audited them
or did business with them?
Why would you
suggest something so dreadful?
If that's not it...
You probably don't take me seriously.
I apologize.
Don't you have any work to do?
I'll speak with each of you
in a one-on-one meeting.
Come to the interview room
when I call your name.
MUN GYEONG-JIN,
CALCULATE SEVERANCE PAY
HOW MUCH TO OPEN
A FRIED CHICKEN STORE?
SHOULD I QUIT?
I WANT TO CRY
INTERVIEW ROOM
Manager Ha Jin-u of Team Two.
It turned into Jurassic Park
in an instant.
Hey, how can you work right now?
Why not? She had a point.
Do specially promoted people
have something in common?
I heard she got promoted three times.
You want to audit
Haemu Pharmaceuticals again?
You're working on something,
aren't you?
What is it? What are they up to?
When I have them
right where I want them
I'll tell you then.
You special promotion jerks.
Can someone get Mr. Ha
a cup of water?
Yes, ma'am.
- I'm useless.
- No, you're not.
Assistant Manager Noh Ki-jun
of Team One?
Okay.
Our meeting will only
last three minutes.
Good. I'm all for efficient meetings.
Let's see, Assistant Manager Noh.
A pretty favorable evaluation.
You've received top evaluations
ever since you joined Haemu.
- I was lucky.
- So it was all luck.
You've handled only the biggest cases
in each subsidiary.
You closed a lot of big ones.
Yes, my luck
followed as I worked hard.
Let's make a minor change
to your role, Mr. Noh.
A special promotion?
Already?
It's not
personnel evaluation season yet.
That doesn't matter.
Well, if that's what you want,
I'll willingly accept...
I'm sending you to Team Three.
What? To Team Three?
You'll transfer to Team Three
and take over the PM cases.
- "PM" is our code for...
- Personal misconduct.
P for personal and M for misconduct.
They're mostly workplace affairs.
You want me to handle
office scandals?
Yes.
Okay, then. That means
today is your new day one.
Ms. Joo, how could you send me
to Team Three to investigate affairs?
I can't understand why.
Why should I help you understand?
I exercised my right
as your superior.
Yes, that's true. But you admitted
that I performed well every year.
You did great.
He's joining us?
I was going to inform you
when things got underway.
I'm working on something
with my team.
It's an important audit
on one of our subsidiaries.
Let me finish it.
Put all the info on our cloud server.
I'll take a look
and allocate someone else.
It follows a complicated logic
and involves many executives.
It requires a very subtle approach.
The only one for the job?
That would be me.
Gosh, this is fun.
Mr. Noh, are you that special?
Do you have some kind of superpower?
Can you fly or teleport?
Can you do the palm blast?
Who do you think you are
that you would be the only person
who can do this particular job?
No way.
Do you actually believe
some employees are irreplaceable?
Apple's doing just fine
after Steve Jobs died.
Do you think
a project will collapse without you?
Audit Team 1, of all teams?
How could you be so utterly naive?
Okay, let's say you were mistaken.
How could you voice that to me?
That's plain arrogance.
I'll let you off today
for making me laugh.
Don't go overtime next time.
Give me a reason, at least.
There must be a reason you want me
to handle affairs.
It's because
you are...
the best one for the job.
Hey, what happened?
I thought she was
going to promote you.
Forget the promotion.
This is more like a demotion.
He's going to Team Three
to investigate affairs of all things.
Still.
They're all nice people.
That's true.
Everyone on Team Three is nice.
Do you need help with anything?
- Do you need help?
- They seem nice.
You'll do fine wherever you go.
Assistant Manager Noh Ki-jun,
the ace of the Audit Team.
Welcome.
How old are you, Mr. Noh?
Still not married?
Or haven't been able to?
The one man here
who gave up on any promotions.
Team Leader Moo Kwang-il.
I heard that people
are reluctant to marry these days.
Consider that a welcome kit.
Look inside.
Bookkeeper Pyun Hae-young
who keeps the team going.
Everything you need is in there.
We usually only give you two pens
but I added one more
out of pity for you.
Once you run out of ink
and need a replacement
you must sign the ledger
before getting a new pen.
Why would you go to such lengths
at a company as big as Haemu?
If you don't like it
blame that fool over there.
You're taking it too far
when all I did was take batteries.
You took a whole pack.
A pack of size AA and AAA each.
The guy is always on the lookout
for things to steal
Manager Cha Sung-tae.
Darn it.
Excuse me, Mr. Noh.
Welcome to Team Three.
If there's anything
you need help with
you can come to me at any time.
Senior Associate Baek Hyun-kyu,
who thinks he's a troubleshooter.
He's called "White Blood Cell"
for some reason.
Oh, and before you sit down,
let me adjust your chair for you.
Right! Assistant Manager Yoon Da-yae
is a part of this team.
An SNU graduate with a certified CPA.
The one with crazy credentials!
Hello, Ms. Yoon.
Ms. Yoon has that Gen Z attitude.
You know what Gen Z is, right?
You can't talk to her.
What in the world is nice
about this team?
I can't believe it.
- Stop it, Manager.
- I...
- That's crazy.
- What did I do?
I...
I can't believe
I'm a part of this team!
Even her parents can't talk to her.
- Why did you take this?
- Quiet.
Dinner's ready.
Will he be late again?
HUBBY
Your call cannot be connected.
You will be redirected to voicemail.
You will be charged after the beep.
WIFEY
Yes?
Yes, I understand. Goodbye.
- How did it go?
- I talked to them.
- They'll meet the deadline.
- Yes!
Nice job.
You've become good
at pressing the vendors now.
It's all thanks to my teacher.
You're getting a call.
Hey, honey. Yes?
Did I forget to mention?
I have a team dinner tonight.
You're having another team dinner?
Yes, I'm sorry. I've been busy.
Hello, ma'am.
It's Jeong Mi-young speaking.
Yes, hello.
It's been a while
since your husband went home early.
We've been too busy
with the task force.
I'll let him leave
as early as possible today.
Hey, honey.
I'll be home early. I'm sorry.
Okay, don't be too late.
Bye.
Jeez.
Who does she think she is
to let my husband go early?
Darn it.
How dare she?
Who does she think she is?
Damn it.
I've had enough.
Mr. Noh.
These four seats are
the tip-off lines.
You'll get lots of calls
so pick up and accept the reports.
- Yes, okay.
- Okay.
You've reached Audit Team One...
No, Audit Team Three.
Hello.
I'm not sure
if I should be bringing this up
but I'm calling
regarding my team leader.
Yes, I see.
Are you looking
to make an internal report?
I mean, my team leader
keeps farting in the office.
It's a bit too much
to hear it go off all day.
It's the worst office environment!
At least give us an air purifier.
I see.
So your team leader farts?
You've reached Audit Team...
You damn asshole!
What took you so long to pick up?
Yet you get paid a fortune,
don't you, you punk?
- ...Three.
- What Three?
You'll only get a grip
when that business goes down!
- Does your company know you do that?
- Sure.
- What would you like to report?
- Report, my ass!
I'll report your damn life!
What's your name?
I'll talk to your chairman
and tell him all about you!
What the heck is your name?
What's your name?
What are these?
Evidence of infidelity!
I had to go through the trash can
to retrieve those.
Yes, so what are...
Where are you going?
Jeez.
Mr. Noh, are you okay?
You looked pale as you ran in.
Is there anyone to pat your back?
If not, I can always come in
for a second.
I'm all right.
Are you sure?
You can take a break
if it's too tough for you.
Nothing beats being healthy.
Let's do proper introductions.
The Head of Audit, Joo In-a.
The former Head of Audit
and the current Director
of Strategic Planning, Kim Han-su.
I've heard a lot about you.
Congratulations on your promotion.
Head of HR, Boo Se-young.
It's been a while, In-a.
We used to work in the same team.
But of course
I started before her.
Hey, Se-young.
You're looking great.
Things must be swell in HR.
You two seem rather close.
That's nice.
This recent appointment was
a genius move, I must say.
We can call our audit teams the sword
of the vice president
and the president.
Someone like Ms. Joo
would be perfect for the job.
Oh, my. How did you know?
I have a knack for swordsmanship.
Ms. Joo has a witty sense of humor.
You'll find it funny
once you get used to it.
How does it feel breathing
the Seoul air again after so long?
The air is the same everywhere.
But the fine dust seems
to have worsened.
So?
Do you regret coming back?
If I do
do I have the option to go back?
Look at the time.
Why don't we grab some dinner...
I have a lot of tasks
to figure out right now.
Why don't we
slice some steak next time?
Yes, sure.
Mr. Vice President.
I'm eating with my parents tonight.
My wife is probably there now.
Goodness, Mr. Vice President.
You're such a romantic.
How's the president doing?
He was discharged last week
but we must keep an eye on him.
I've been
checking his condition frequently.
Your call cannot be connected.
You will be redirected...
- Your call cannot be connected...
- Darn it.
WHY AREN'T YOU ANSWERING MY CALL?
PLEASE CALL ME
Why aren't you picking up?
Please call me.
Why aren't you answering my call?
Give me a call.
Are you still having dinner?
Honey, when are you coming home?
When are you coming home?
Damn it!
All right, now.
Our best duo, Mr. Son
and Ms. Jeong.
You know that
the launch of the new brand
will decide the fate
of Haemu Foods, don't you?
- Yes.
- I need you two
to work together
and do your best as a team.
- I'll do my best.
- So will I.
- Can you really do it?
- I'll do my best!
Now, cheers!
- Cheers!
Let's do this!
- Cheers.
- Good luck.
That's nice.
Did you drink yesterday, too?
I really wanted
to keep myself from drinking tonight.
This meat looks nice.
It's beef we're talking about.
Your call cannot be connected.
You will be redirected to voicemail.
- Damn it.
- You will be charged after the beep.
Darn it.
The work is...
Honey!
I'm sorry.
Darn it.
Jeez.
Your call cannot be connected.
You will be redirected...
What the... Open the door.
Hey! Open the door right now!
I'll kill you.
Open the door! Hey!
Honey.
What are you doing?
Heading home now?
He's so out of it.
He's become a different man
in just a day.
- All right!
Great job.
ANXIOUSLY WAITING FOR THE RESULT
CHUNG SANG-HYEON
DROPS FROM 2 STARS TO 1 STAR
The accuracy
of your dance dropped quite a lot
in the verse...
No rank lasts forever in this world.
Hence
the higher your ranking
the more anxious you become.
You're such an embarrassment.
How did you know I was there?
Did you snoop around
every restaurant I might be in?
Why didn't you pick up your phone?
I was having a team dinner!
Can't you pick up your phone
while you eat?
My phone?
Right. You're always
cooped up at home.
You wouldn't understand anything
about work life.
You drive me crazy! Damn it.
If you do not wish to remain weak...
you must fight your way up.
What do you mean...
In the end, keeping your rank
means survival.
Don't lose heart.
Leave no regrets.
What? How did he not make it?
Not only is he
a good singer and a good dancer
but he's good-looking
and is good at everything!
But he's a total ace.
How did he not make it?
How come?
Why?
Excuse me, Mr. Noh.
She has something to report
to the Audit Team.
She's been waiting
since early morning.
It looks like
my husband is having an affair.
Goodness.
When my husband brought home
perfume as a birthday gift,
I knew something was off.
Wait, what about the perfume?
No one buys a perfume
for a married man.
What do you think that means?
It means she wants to mark him
with that scent.
She wants her man
to smell like something she picked.
I've kept my eyes on my husband
since that day
and he never leaves his phone.
He even takes it into the shower.
I read online that it definitely
means he's having an affair.
And they're always working together.
Not only do they
always go on business trips together
but they even message
each other at night.
Right. I have evidence, too.
It's a strand of hair.
I found it on my husband's shirt.
It must belong to that woman.
I know it.
Ma'am, we can't call this evidence...
We'll investigate
and get back to you right away.
Okay.
What?
We must go through the formalities
after receiving a report.
We have to do the paperwork
and talk to the person in question.
What is it? Go and check.
Go, now.
What am I supposed to check?
Should I run a DNA test
on this hair or what?
Come on.
Anyway
wasn't Mr. Son's wife
really frightening last night?
She came all the way there
just because he didn't pick up.
She apparently suspects something
is going on with Ms. Jeong.
Ms. Jeong must feel so wronged.
All she ever does is work.
But I think I understand why.
Couples only see each other
briefly at night.
But you're with work colleagues
all day long
and share more in common.
And you talk to them much more.
I would be concerned, too.
I don't think I'd like that either.
But there are limits.
She was almost delusional.
Gosh. What is this?
She was infamous.
FOOD BRAND PLANNING TEAM
Director Kang will kill us
if we continue like this.
They're exactly
what we agreed to during the meeting.
- Stop making random changes.
- I don't see the point!
Comparing them with domestic brands
isn't what we're doing.
I kept saying that our focus is
on expanding into the global market!
They're just colleagues.
There isn't any affair.
- What?
- Don't you remember?
Let's analyze all corporations
making under a billion won.
- We have to do this.
- Yes, ma'am.
There are some discrepancies
in the business licenses, so...
I see. Really?
Mr. Noh. Come here. Hurry.
- Are we all here?
- Yes.
All right, then. We received
a very important assignment
directly from the top.
- Our team?
- From the top?
Yes, so that means
we must pause whatever we were doing
and handle this first.
This may turn into a criminal case
and blow up into a big story
if anyone outside hears about it.
It must remain confidential
as we resolve the matter
as quietly as possible.
Do you understand?
What is it?
ON-SITE AUDIT TEAM SURVEY
HAEMU GROUP AUDIT TEAM 3
So you're saying
there's poppy here?
Goodness, man.
I told you to be quiet.
The security guard said
he found a poppy out back
while cleaning up the flower bed.
Not the field poppy
but the other kind.
He thinks there may be more
in another place
so we must handle this quietly
before it becomes trouble, okay?
A pharmaceutical company
with a poppy?
Did you eat that flower?
Don't go around eating random stuff
just because it's free.
Goodness. Just keep looking.
- Hello?
- It's Mr. Son's wife calling.
Have you checked the hair?
I'll e-mail you the result.
I'm on a different assignment,
so I must hang up.
Yes?
You said you'd get back to me
after investigating.
I was right, about Ms. Jeong, right?
What will happen to them now?
The company must
handle this strictly to...
Please stop!
Nothing is going on between them.
They're only working hard
even as we speak!
They're together again?
- Did you see them?
- Ma'am.
Please stop pestering me.
You should go see the doctor.
You know, you're being delusional!
You got poop on yourself.
Jeez.
Is the rehearsal
in the conference room?
Yes, I called everyone
and said we were on our way.
- One second.
- Sure.
Thank you.
2. TARGET
SON MYUNG-SOO, JEONG MI-YOUNG
3. METHOD
INTERVIEW, E-MAIL LOGS, CCTV
I hope you bloom and blossom
in this crappy office.
Goodness, Mr. Noh.
Are you getting off now?
I read your report
on Mr. Son Myung-soo's case.
Are you sure that's it?
Are you sure
they aren't having an affair?
No.
How can I be sure
of what's happening between them?
There's no hard evidence
so the circumstantial evidence
points to nothing.
I like how you don't make up crap.
But if this is only between them,
shouldn't you look more into it?
- Hello.
- Food Brand Planning Team?
- Yes.
Are you working overtime?
- Hello.
- Thanks for your hard work.
But I don't see
Mr. Son and Ms. Jeong.
They're getting ready
for the presentation.
We're stepping out to eat dinner.
Is that so?
How do you know everyone in our team?
You're just as they say,
Almighty Joo.
- Almighty Joo?
- It means you have your eyes
on everything and know everything.
Goodness, people say that?
That's crazy.
What? "Almighty Joo"?
But I do know that the Brand Team
is doing something very important.
Okay, since you're all working hard
until late in the night
so I, Almighty Joo, will treat you
to something expensive and delicious!
You are the Almighty Joo!
I'll have it delivered here
for all of you to enjoy
so you can go back upstairs.
- Thank you.
Good luck.
- Thank you!
Mr. Noh,
I need a new report from you.
Sorry?
I really must be Almighty Joo.
That's a great nickname.
Why don't we go over our moves again?
Yes, Mr. Son.
But...
what moves do you mean?
Something like this.
What do you mean
you need a new report from me?
You'll find out by tomorrow.
No, maybe today.
Darn it.
Are you all right?
What about you?
What was that?
Darn it.
Mrs. Son...
What did you say?
Delusional?
Damn it.
Why are you only blaming me?
I'm not the one who's crazy.
That asshole and bitch are!
I'm going to kill them.
FILING FOR LOVE
GUEST APPEARANCE
BY PARK HA-SUN, KIM JONG-TAE
Mr. Noh is the pride of our team!
He says you're the pride.
How brazen.
If only everyone else were like you
this world would've been
a much better place.
You're a fool
Do your next assignment right.
It's Zone F in level four
of the basement parking lot.
- We need to expose them.
- Expose?
How am I going to do that?
Morals? Do you think
you're a police officer or a judge?
Do you hate her that much?
Should I just quit?
You should've talked to me
if you wanted to leave the Audit Team
instead of talking behind my back.
Subtitles by Eunsook Youn
and Jennifer Lim